<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://whatever.todds.cooking/index.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <title>whatever todd&#x27;s cooking</title>
    <link>https://whatever.todds.cooking</link>
    <description>A blog about whatever, todd's cooking</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyright 2023 whatever.todds.cooking</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Jan, 2023 08:08:24 -08:00</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>whatever.todds.cooking</generator>
    <ttl>40</ttl>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Potato Tacos & Salsa</title>
      <description>Today is one of those days where I woke up at 5:30 AM filled with the kind of existential dread that only millenials feel like they know (it’s OK millenials, Generation X is used to being forgotten) and now it’s nearly 8 PM and I worked all day, cooked for two hours, haven’t even showered, but here</description>
      <pubDate>Wednesday, May 19, 2021</pubDate>
      <guid>https://whatever.todds.cooking/sweet_tater_tacos.html</guid>
      <link>https://whatever.todds.cooking/sweet_tater_tacos.html</link>
      <source url="https://whatever.todds.cooking">whatever, todd's cooking</source>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pizza Night</title>
      <description>When I say pizza, you say time!
PIZZA!
[tries to mumble through a mouth full of pizza] TIME!
PIZZA!
[choking on pizza, turning blue] TIME!
PIZZA!
PIZZA!
PIZZA?
Well that didn’t go as planned.  But the pizza did.
So last spring during the first of these many, many shutdowns we’ve endured, I really</description>
      <pubDate>Saturday, May 15, 2021</pubDate>
      <guid>https://whatever.todds.cooking/pizza.html</guid>
      <link>https://whatever.todds.cooking/pizza.html</link>
      <source url="https://whatever.todds.cooking">whatever, todd's cooking</source>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pork Chops, Cabbage & Asparagus</title>
      <description>Well my fucking mom wrote me and told me that I shouldn’t swear as goddamn much (or at all) in my blog.
We all know what I say to that!
Fuck that shit!
Not that I have a Pabst with me, but like I dunno, my fucking neighbor definitely does so I should just roll down the street.
I guess it’s pretty</description>
      <pubDate>Friday, May 14, 2021</pubDate>
      <guid>https://whatever.todds.cooking/pork-chops-aparagus.html</guid>
      <link>https://whatever.todds.cooking/pork-chops-aparagus.html</link>
      <source url="https://whatever.todds.cooking">whatever, todd's cooking</source>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fish Tacos</title>
      <description>Tacobouta great dinner!
I had about a half a mind to leave the post there and go on with my night, but I’m not that much of a tease. After taking the entire week off for my birthday last week (from work and from cooking) I realized I missed making dinner so here I am again, slaving over a grill,</description>
      <pubDate>Tuesday, May 11, 2021</pubDate>
      <guid>https://whatever.todds.cooking/fish-tacos.html</guid>
      <link>https://whatever.todds.cooking/fish-tacos.html</link>
      <source url="https://whatever.todds.cooking">whatever, todd's cooking</source>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steak & Salad with Buttermilk Ranch</title>
      <description>I took the fucking week off because it was my birthday on one of them, so the last thing I cooked (other than some of the best grilled cheeses you’ll ever eat), was like a week ago? I dunno, time is a fucking construct.
Also my partner was supposed to guest blog on Wednesday because she made dinner</description>
      <pubDate>Friday, May  7, 2021</pubDate>
      <guid>https://whatever.todds.cooking/steak-salad.html</guid>
      <link>https://whatever.todds.cooking/steak-salad.html</link>
      <source url="https://whatever.todds.cooking">whatever, todd's cooking</source>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Lo Mein</title>
      <description>One of my kids got a magic kit at the toy store today while they were getting a present for their friend’s birthday and I’m really sad to say it doesn’t have any tricks about eating all your goddamn food in it. Does anyone know if someone makes a kit like that? If so, please, for the love of god</description>
      <pubDate>Wednesday, Apr 28, 2021</pubDate>
      <guid>https://whatever.todds.cooking/chicken-lomein.html</guid>
      <link>https://whatever.todds.cooking/chicken-lomein.html</link>
      <source url="https://whatever.todds.cooking">whatever, todd's cooking</source>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shepherd's Pie with Carrots</title>
      <description>Before I even start, will all the pedantic assholes please raise your hands? Now, everyone who has a hand up, get fucked. I say this with all the love in my heart because I have learned that apparently you can’t call it Shepherd’s Pie unless it contains ground lamb. And guess what? There ain’t no</description>
      <pubDate>Tuesday, Apr 27, 2021</pubDate>
      <guid>https://whatever.todds.cooking/shepards-pie.html</guid>
      <link>https://whatever.todds.cooking/shepards-pie.html</link>
      <source url="https://whatever.todds.cooking">whatever, todd's cooking</source>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smoked Tomatillo Chili</title>
      <description>


“Follow the smoke to the riff filled land”


You know I tried to smoke tomatillos yesterday, but I couldn’t like the joint because they were so wet? I’ll never figure out how someone can even light a brisket.
Oh god is this post just going to be filled with lame attempts at weed jokes?
Don’t you</description>
      <pubDate>Monday, Apr 26, 2021</pubDate>
      <guid>https://whatever.todds.cooking/smoked-chili.html</guid>
      <link>https://whatever.todds.cooking/smoked-chili.html</link>
      <source url="https://whatever.todds.cooking">whatever, todd's cooking</source>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grilled Sausages, Broccoli Rabe & Potatoes</title>
      <description>I’ve been trying to come up with a funny hook all week to write about this meal and either it was way too obvious and full of boring sexual innuendo (sausage party is so over used too) or it was some inanely long and boring drivel, which like, I get it, that’s the whole point of this blog, but even</description>
      <pubDate>Sunday, Apr 25, 2021</pubDate>
      <guid>https://whatever.todds.cooking/grilling.html</guid>
      <link>https://whatever.todds.cooking/grilling.html</link>
      <source url="https://whatever.todds.cooking">whatever, todd's cooking</source>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Fajitas</title>
      <description>We have had a spate of fantastic weather recently here in Seattle which means it’s been clobbering grilling time because as I intoned earlier, I would much rather be sweating outside over something hot than sweating inside over something hot. And lets face it, I’m always going to be sweating so</description>
      <pubDate>Tuesday, Apr 20, 2021</pubDate>
      <guid>https://whatever.todds.cooking/chicken-fajitas.html</guid>
      <link>https://whatever.todds.cooking/chicken-fajitas.html</link>
      <source url="https://whatever.todds.cooking">whatever, todd's cooking</source>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dinners for the Week of April 19</title>
      <description>This was a busy weekend in blog-land but ideally you won’t notice a single difference! I re-wrote the software that I use to generate this blog and finally got it back to working in this new language. (If you’re at all curious, the software and the raw data for the blog are linked at the bottom of</description>
      <pubDate>Monday, Apr 19, 2021</pubDate>
      <guid>https://whatever.todds.cooking/dinners-week-april-19.html</guid>
      <link>https://whatever.todds.cooking/dinners-week-april-19.html</link>
      <source url="https://whatever.todds.cooking">whatever, todd's cooking</source>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eggplant, Cauliflower &amp; Asparagus</title>
      <description>I promise every time I don’t write something for a bit I’m not going to start it off with some trite been a long time since I rapped at ya bullshit, but fuck.  I got my second Pfizer vaccine on Monday AM and by Monday night I was in bed, fever, chills and totally laid up for a good 36 hours, so </description>
      <pubDate>Saturday, Apr 17, 2021</pubDate>
      <guid>https://whatever.todds.cooking/eggplant-cauliflower-asparagus.html</guid>
      <link>https://whatever.todds.cooking/eggplant-cauliflower-asparagus.html</link>
      <source url="https://whatever.todds.cooking">whatever, todd's cooking</source>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ain't No Party Like A Taco Party</title>
      <description>Because a taco party doesn’t something, something, something.
What’s the biggest problem a vegan crossfit person has when they meet someone new?
Trying to decide to tell them they’re vegan or they do crossfit first!
Wait. I can do better.
How can you tell someone is vegan?
Don’t worry  THE</description>
      <pubDate>Sunday, Apr 11, 2021</pubDate>
      <guid>https://whatever.todds.cooking/tacos-party.html</guid>
      <link>https://whatever.todds.cooking/tacos-party.html</link>
      <source url="https://whatever.todds.cooking">whatever, todd's cooking</source>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phở Gà</title>
      <description>We’re going fucking ✨ IN ✨ TER ✨ NA ✨ TION ✨ AL ✨ tonight so strap the fuck in and hold on to your goddamn cloth masks you sons of bitches.


You&#x27;re gonna need a bigger bowl

Nah, I just made some goddamn soup. Sure, its got a fancy name with all those diacritical marks (what a colonial legacy of</description>
      <pubDate>Thursday, Apr  8, 2021</pubDate>
      <guid>https://whatever.todds.cooking/pho.html</guid>
      <link>https://whatever.todds.cooking/pho.html</link>
      <source url="https://whatever.todds.cooking">whatever, todd's cooking</source>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Challah & Scalloped Potatoes</title>
      <description>It’s already goddamn Wednesday morning and I just got did the shopping for the week which means a) we’ve had take out or leftovers since Sunday (I might be part ham at this point) and b) work has been kicking my ass and I’m off my fucking game. This week’s menu will probably include:

Phở </description>
      <pubDate>Wednesday, Apr  7, 2021</pubDate>
      <guid>https://whatever.todds.cooking/challah.html</guid>
      <link>https://whatever.todds.cooking/challah.html</link>
      <source url="https://whatever.todds.cooking">whatever, todd's cooking</source>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eggs, Bacon & Toast</title>
      <description>There are only a few things in this world that I prefer to make if I’m going to eat it and scrambled eggs are probably at the top of that list, especially since I moved to Seattle. Pre-pandemic it was difficult to find a place that made scrambled eggs that weren’t just downright overcooked or like,</description>
      <pubDate>Saturday, Apr  3, 2021</pubDate>
      <guid>https://whatever.todds.cooking/eggs-bacon.html</guid>
      <link>https://whatever.todds.cooking/eggs-bacon.html</link>
      <source url="https://whatever.todds.cooking">whatever, todd's cooking</source>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saag Paneer & Laacha Paratha</title>
      <description>I know, I know, I know I made this on like Sunday and it’s already Florpsday this week I’m so fucking behind I’m an ass.
Get it?
Behind?
Ass?
LOL.
What can I say it’s been a really busy work at week. Week at work. Whatever. It’s been so busy I’ve been punting on making meals which means that post I</description>
      <pubDate>Wednesday, Mar 31, 2021</pubDate>
      <guid>https://whatever.todds.cooking/saag-paneer.html</guid>
      <link>https://whatever.todds.cooking/saag-paneer.html</link>
      <source url="https://whatever.todds.cooking">whatever, todd's cooking</source>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dinners for the Week of March 29</title>
      <description>In rotation this week:

Ground meat chili with beans
Pan pizzas and a salad. Not deep dish, but like remember when you were a kid and you’d go to Pizza Hut and they had those tall blue plastic cups and the red and white checkered plastic tablecloths? No? Me neither. My mom would sometimes order in</description>
      <pubDate>Sunday, Mar 28, 2021</pubDate>
      <guid>https://whatever.todds.cooking/dinners_week_march_28.html</guid>
      <link>https://whatever.todds.cooking/dinners_week_march_28.html</link>
      <source url="https://whatever.todds.cooking">whatever, todd's cooking</source>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roast Beef, Mashed Potatoes, Yorkshire Pudding, Sautéed Corn & Mushroom-Onion Gravy</title>
      <description>I forgot to take photos of most of this meal, so like, I dunno, maybe I’m making it all up.  But I had two missions for today:

Make up for the “Christmas Incident”
Convince our friend that mashed potatoes are Actually Good

I accomplished at least one of those goals so in your face “Saint” Nick.</description>
      <pubDate>Sunday, Mar 28, 2021</pubDate>
      <guid>https://whatever.todds.cooking/roast-beef.html</guid>
      <link>https://whatever.todds.cooking/roast-beef.html</link>
      <source url="https://whatever.todds.cooking">whatever, todd's cooking</source>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lamb Kabobs, Cauliflower & Hazelnut Salad, Labneh</title>
      <description>Well, the downside of the new kitchen is that the hood fan works well enough that I can no longer use the smoke detectors as an alert when the cooking is done. The upside is that the neighbors no longer think I’m a pyromaniac. Which is exactly what a pyromaniac would want them to think. I think we</description>
      <pubDate>Friday, Mar 26, 2021</pubDate>
      <guid>https://whatever.todds.cooking/lamb-cauliflower.html</guid>
      <link>https://whatever.todds.cooking/lamb-cauliflower.html</link>
      <source url="https://whatever.todds.cooking">whatever, todd's cooking</source>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
